《女子监狱》
第二季第四集
该死
Shit.
抱歉  罗莎小姐  这车里简直是冷死了
Sorry, Miss Rosa. It's colder than an Eskimo's nuts in here!
我想开空调暖暖  但如果调得太高
I'm trying to get the heat going, but when I turn it up too high,
会吹出一股怪味儿
a real bad smell comes out of the blowers.
好像是老鼠屎  它们住在引擎里
I think it's mouse shit. You know, they live in the engine.
别呼进去就好
Just don't breathe in.
我要去注射毒药了
I'm going to get poison pumped into my veins.
吸进去点老鼠屎算什么
What's a little mouse shit in my lungs?
都好了吗  系好安全带
All set? Seat belts on.
婚礼筹划得怎么样了
How's wedding planning going?
我们要等一阵  就是暂时搁置一下
We're holdin' off for a minute. Just pressin' the pause button.
要来的人太多了  我有个大家庭
Too many people wanna come, you know? I got a big family.
我是指人数多  不是说他们胖
Big, number-wise, not big fat.
不过  也有几个挺胖的
Although, there are some fatties.
而且在这里预定供货商也比较困难
And it's hard for me to book all the vendors from in here.
他们都不在我的许可通话名单上
You know, none of 'em are on my approved call list.
婚礼对我来说就是厄运  我丈夫都死了
Weddings were bad luck for me. All my husbands died.
有几个啊
How many were there?
两个  第三个我不肯跟他结婚
Two. The third one I wouldn't marry.
如果你知道自己被诅咒了  就不去犯那个冲
Once you know you got a curse on you, you can work around it.
他住在卡纳西
He lives in Canarsie.
这我还不知道呢  你从没说过你的事
I didn't know that. You never talk about your life.
也没人在乎
Nobody cares.
你还要服刑多久
How much time you got left?
两年多
More than two years.
你还年轻漂亮  还有大好人生
You're still young, pretty. You got your whole life ahead of you.
我呢
Me?
我要死在这儿了
I'm gonna die here.
你去哪了
Where the heck have you been?
去看电影了
At the movies.
好啊  大白天去看电影  看什么了
Perfect. In the middle of the day. What'd you see?
-《暮光之城》  -这都第14遍了吧
- Twilight. - For what, the 14th time?
你的小日子过得真清闲啊
Don't you live the fuckin' life of leisure?
你两个噪音制造器
Hey, Noise Pollution One and Two,
我还想看电视呢
I'm trying to watch my program here.
让孩子都出去玩
And send those kids outside.
麦克  大点声
Mikey, turn it up.
妈按铃都按了一小时了
Ma's been ringing her bell for an hour.
我是灰姑娘吗
What am I, Cinderella?
该你了
It is your turn!
我今早给她洗过床单了  屎尿一堆
I cleaned her sheets this morning. Piss and everything.
看好你的孩子啊  他能活到现在真是奇迹
Watch your baby, would you? It's a miracle he's lived this long.
罗娜  罗娜
Lorna! Lorna!
是你吗
That you?
好了
All right.
喂  你好  我从你家买了双鞋
Hello. Yes. I purchased a pair of shoes from you.
订单号11006178
Order 1-1-0-0-6-1-7-8,
一双拼缀普拉达
a pair of patchwork platform Pradas.
嗯  我知道我付钱了
Yeah, I can see that my card has been charged,
但我没收到鞋
but I never received them.
我没搬家  没错  我留的就是这个地址
No, I haven't moved. Yeah! That's the address I gave you.
不  我不是说你没寄来
No... I'm not accusing you of not having sent them,
但我就是没收到
but the fact is they never came.
是啊  的确不幸  我还要去参加派对呢
Yes, yes, it is unfortunate, 'cause I had this big party to go to
这下只能穿上一季的旧款缪缪了
and I had to wear last season's Miu Miu's.
普拉达的副线品牌
不  我不想要你们再寄一双来
No. No, I don't want another pair.
我想退钱  嗯  没错  全款退款
I want a refund. Yeah, that's right. A full refund.
多谢你如此诚实  真的很感谢
Aw, thank you for your honesty, I really appreciate it.
是的  我来告诉你我的卡号
Yes. Yes, I do have my card number.
看那个女的
Check this bitch out.
脸化成那样居然没人开枪打她
I'm surprised she doesn't get a shot for putting on that face.
如果警察心情不好  会有人打她的
If the cop's in a bad mood, she does.
最近有好多人化蓝眼影和涂红口红
I'm seeing a lot of blue eye-shadow and red lipstick.
不是物资部卖的  是谁在进东西
It's not coming out of commissary. Who's importing around here?
现在违禁物品不多了
Oh, not really a lot of contraband these days.
红妈的生意被取缔后就没多少了
Not since Red got shut down.
红妈
Red, huh?
那倒也是
Well, that figures.
但这里肯定有人在钻空子
Still, there's gotta be some holes in this cheese.
有人在偷运东西进来
Somebody is bringing in something.
珀比会勾兑烈酒
Well, Poussey makes hooch.
常有万金油
And Chang, she got that Tiger Balm,
但别抹在嘴唇上  或是眼睛上
but don't put it on your lips, or your eyeballs.
别那么干啊
Bad idea.
烈酒
Hooch, huh?
味道恶心死了  像是吐出来的果汁酒
Shit tastes nasty. It's like vomit wine coolers.
里面有酷爱  快腐烂的水果
Yo... It's got Kool-Aid, old fruit,
番茄酱和发霉面包
ketchup, and moldy bread.
她卖这个吗
She sells that?
我喝不下  让我觉得怪怪的  头晕
I can't drink it. Makes me feel funny, makes my head all fuzzy.
你还带着那东西
You still carting that shit around?
你个一根筋的混蛋
You one determined mo-fo.
那是什么
What the fuck is that?
-尿管  -什么
- It's a pee funnel. - A what?
我不想再在脏马桶上蹲着了
I'm tired of trying to pop a squat over them nasty-ass toilets.
用这个装置能轻松一些
This rig is gonna make it easy.
你别犯傻了  你要怎么用啊
Girl, that's crazy. How you gonna use that?
用这个  我就能站着尿了  像男人一样
Yo, with this, I can pee standing up. Like a dude.
把这个放在我私处这儿
Take this part, put it over my stuff.
然后把管子的部分伸进马桶里
Take this little tube part, put it in the toilet.
就是放在正上方  多天才啊
Or, you know what I'm saying, right over it. It's genius, yo!
我要管它叫"站逍遥"
I'm gonna call it the "Stand and deliver."
你该马上申请专利
You should call the patent office right now
挣个几百万的
and make a million dollars.
真的
Really?
当然不了  这是我听过的最蠢的主意了
Hell, no! That's the stupidest idea I ever heard.
才不是  马桶大早上凉死了
No, it ain't, man. Them toilets be cold as fuck in the morning.
等着瞧吧  大家都会抢着要的
You'll see. Everybody gonna be wanting one of these to piss in.
拜托  我们在吃饭呢
Please. We're eating.
我得找个防水的胶带什么的
Yeah, I just gotta find me some waterproof tape or something
把这两部分粘起来
to get these two parts together.
你要那个漏斗做什么
I don't see why you need the funnel.
你直接把管子插进去不就行了吗
Like, can't you just put the tube up in you?
不行啊  尿不是从那儿出来的啊
Uh, no. 'Cause that's not where the pee comes out.
当然是了啊
Uh, yeah, it do.
-从大洞里出来  -是啊
- Out of the big hole. - Yeah.
不是啊  还有一个洞洞的
No, y'all. There's a different hole.
-尿洞吗  -对啊
- For pee? - Yeah.
什么  你疯了吧
What? You crazy.
真的  除了主要的那个洞洞
Y'all, there is the main coochie hole
还有一个专门用来尿尿的小洞洞
and then there's, like, another little hole just for pee.
-少来了  -得了吧
- Nah! - Nah!
你们没上过性教育课吗
Didn't y'all take Sex Ed?
她说得对  有一个超小的尿洞洞
She's right. There's an eeny-meeny-weeny-weeny pee hole.
你们是嗑药磕傻了吗
Man, you trippin'.
都是从一个洞洞里出来的  阴道洞
It all come out the same hole. The vagina hole.
好吧  那么你们
All right, then how come you
塞着卫生棉的时候怎么也能尿尿
can still pee when you got a tampon in?
告诉你们  有两个洞洞
I'm telling you, there's two holes.
是三个
Three holes.
还有屁眼
The butt.
行了  你们都恶心死了  我走了
All right. You are all disgusting. I'm out.
我才不要听你们说呢
I am not even gonna entertain this conversation.
苏珊娜  来吗
Suzanne! You coming?
给我下个单
Put my order in.
我都糊涂了  到底在哪啊
I am so confused. Where is it at?
我还是看不到你说的那个啊
Yo, I still don't see what the hell you talkin' about!
你知道你做爱的那个洞洞吧
You know, your hole, like, your sex hole.
阴道洞  当然知道
The vagina hole. Yeah, I got that.
你们都疯了
Y'all are crazy.
真希望我有个手机都给你们拍下来
Man, I wish I had a phone to record this shit.
看你的阴蒂下面  主洞前面
Now, look underneath your clit, before the main hole.
或者是上面的里侧
Or like, just inside the top of it.
我还是什么都看不到啊
Man, I still can't see shit down here.
有好多一层层的东西
It's like too many, like, flappy-flap thingies.
-天呐  -你是怎么知道的
- Oh, God. - How do you know all this?
我近距离看到过足够多的女人私处
Yo, I've been up close and personal with my share of pussy.
你要我指给你看吗
Yeah, you want me to just show you?
不用  我自己来就行  告诉我在哪
No! No, no, no. I can do it. Just, just tell me where.
就在大洞洞里头
Okay, right inside the big ol' hole
还有一个洞洞  一个小洞洞
there's another hole. Like, a little one.
什么  我以为是完全独立的另一个洞洞呢
Wait, what? I thought you said it was a whole other hole.
是洞洞里面的洞洞
It's a hole in a hole.
天呐  那个洞不是在洞洞里
For the love of God, girls, the hole is not inside the hole.
你有阴道  然后有阴蒂
You have your vagina proper, then you have your clitoris.
尿道在阴蒂和阴道之间
The urethra is located between the clit and the vagina,
在小阴唇里
inside the labia minora.
-真的假的  -真的
- For real? - For real.
我自己设计过一个  都画好图纸了
I designed one myself. Had plans drawn up and everything.
我当年见过不少奇形怪状的阴道
I seen some funky punani in my day.
我才不要听天由命呢
I'm not gonna leave that shit up to chance.
给  好好照照看  你会看到的
Here. Take a long look, honey. You'll see what I'm talking about.
天呐  我操啊
Oh, my God. Holy shit!
她说得对啊
Yo, y'all, she's right.
好可爱啊
It's cute.
-我要下个看  -我也要
- I'm next! - Yeah! Me, too.
-我一定得看看  -别过来
- You know, I gotta see this shit! - Yo! Back up!
尼古拉斯  你怎么回事
Nichols! What the fuck?
你怎么把小美人都捡走了
Why you pickin' all the peaches?
-我不知道你在说什么  -你很清楚
- I have no idea what you're talking about. - Yes, you do.
霍斯克沃茨
Hascowitz?
我想上她都想了一个月了
I've been trying to get bumper-to-bumper with that for a month.
现在呢  她觉得被人利用了
And now, she feels used
不愿随便跟人睡了  因为你先上了她
and doesn't wanna sleep around because you got there first.
被利用了
Used, eh?
我上她的时候她又不是个雏
She wasn't exactly new when I rode in her, eh?
都有点受损了
A little dented actually, right?
内壁都磨坏了
The upholstery was worn.
你知道我想要她的
You knew I was after that.
没办法  不是所有人都喜欢爷们型的
Well, what can I say? Not everyone wants a diesel dyke.
别碰我看好的人
Lay off my marks.
说真的  别到处搅和了  这是什么
Seriously. Enough with the cliterference. What's this?
给我还回来  还给我
Put that back, please. Would you give it back?
谁是布鲁克  是新来的那个是吗
Who is Brook? Oh, yeah. That's the new girl, isn't it?
话唠的性感亚裔人
Hot one of the Asian persuasion?
天呐  这是你的性爱记录册吗
Oh, my God! I found your fuck book?
是又如何
Right. So what if it is?
你真是上瘾了
Oh, you fuckin' junkie.
-行了  -我理解的
- All right. - No, I get this.
喜欢妹子总比毒品强  是吧
Better pussy than smack. Right?
我才没上瘾呢  只是收集而已
It's not an addiction. It's a collection, all right?
有些人收集扣子
Some people collect buttons
或是塔可钟的吉娃娃  我收集高潮
or Taco Bell Chihuahuas, I collect orgasms.
我一心为人付出
See, I'm all about giving.
我简直是舔洞界的特蕾莎修女
Look, I am like a bean-flicking Mother Teresa.
跟你说  我就喜欢这种比赛
You know what? This here is my kind of competition.
我们赌定了  贱人  瞧好吧
It's on. Ooh! Bitch, this is on!
罗莎小姐是怎么回事
So, what's the deal with Miss Rosa?
我知道她有癌症
I mean, I know they say she has cancer and everything,
但真的不是秃头症吗
but are they sure it's not alopecia?
而且这个房间是怎么回事啊
And what's the deal with this room?
这里都住的是新来的  或是生病的
Is everyone in here, like, new or sick
或是老人吗
or just old?
我简直不敢相信这里面有多少老人
I mean, I can't believe how many old people there are in here.
她们是做了什么居然还在这儿
Like, what did they do that they're still in here?
比如  她犯了什么事
Like, what did she do?
不管你事  你个疯婆子
None of your fuckin' business, you mental patient.
说真的  她们都是70年代就关进来了吗
But seriously, have they all been in here since, like, the '70s?
不  他们大都是表现良好从重刑监狱转过来的
No, most of them got transferred up from Max for good behavior.
想想她们在这儿
It is crazy to think about
待了多少年  真是疯狂啊
how many years they spend in here, you know?
我以前也被逮捕过好几次
I mean, I've been arrested before, like loads of times.
他们清理祖科提公园时
When they cleared out Zuccotti Park,
我在号子里蹲了三天
I spent three whole days in a cell.
那只是拘留所  这可是监狱
But that was jail and this is prison.
其实差不多了
They're pretty much the same thing.
不是的  蹲拘留所你爸爸妈妈会去接你
No, they're not. Your parents pick you up from jail.
把她的电池拿出来吧
Take out her batteries, would ya?
我还想打个盹呢
I'm trying to take a nap over here.
查普曼  苏苏  去A区玩得愉快
Chapman, Soso, happy day in cell block A,
你们被分配过去了
you are being assigned.
等等  我们做错什么了吗
Wait, did we do something wrong?
不  是分配床铺了
No. We're getting our bunks.
好啊
Oh, cool beans.
天呐  那么我们要做室友了吗
Oh, my God, does that mean we're gonna be roomies?
我得告诉你  我有时会打鼾
Just so you know, I do snore sometimes, so...
但只是仰睡或感冒的时候
But only if I'm on my back or if I have a cold.
提醒我翻个身  我会照做的
So, just tell me to roll over, and I totally will.
-早啊  贝尔警官  -奥尼尔
- Morning, Officer Bell. - O'Neill.
没想到铺位这么有宿舍的感觉
I didn't expect the bunks to feel so dorm-y.
让我联想到了露营
It kind of reminds me of camp, you know?
就是没有花边手链和射箭  有点悲哀
Except without the gimp bracelets and the archery and kind of sad.
真他妈是一群秃鹰
What a bunch of vultures.
你这是偷了本书吗
Wait, did you just steal that book?
是我的  我只是要回来
It's mine. I'm reclaiming it.
查普曼  这里  苏苏  跟我来
Chapman, in here. Soso, follow me.
我们没分在一起吗
We're not together?
谢谢你
Thank you.
你去过夏令营吗
Did you go to summer camp?
那真是我一生中最美好的时光了
It was seriously, like, the best time of my life.
你好啊  红妈
Hi, Red.
不  亲爱的  你不住这儿
Oh, no, honey, you're not in here.
看来我是住这儿
Looks like I am.
我能把那些搬开吗
Can I move some of this stuff?
不行
No, you may not.
能给我几个挂衣钩吗
Can I have a few of those hooks then?
四个我都要用  那都是我的
I need all four of them. They're mine.
你能怎么样  不给我吃的吗
What are you gonna do? Not feed me?
我这儿闹粉蚧灾了
I have a mealy bug infestation.
它们会分泌一种粉末蜡状物质
They secrete this powdery wax substance.
特别不好弄下来
It's a bitch to get off.
-你给我安排了室友  -是啊
- You gave me a roommate. - Yes, I did.
我都12年没有铺友了
I haven't had a bunkie in 12 years.
把监狱工作
We don't get special privileges
变成毒品走私生意的人
when we turn our prison assignment
别想要特权
into a drug smuggling operation.
你知道我从不干那个
You know that was never my game.
好啊  赖在一个不能来为自己辩护的人身上吧
Sure, pin it on a guy who's not here to defend himself.
他就指着这一点呢
He was counting on that.
你实在是贪心不足  红妈
You got too big for your britches, Red.
我们都睁一只眼闭一只眼
We all turned the other way.
你带连裤袜和指甲油进来
You were bringing in pantyhose and nail polish.
那都无所谓  女囚也开心
Seemed harmless, kept the ladies happy.
海利  他脑袋埋在你屁股里那么深
And Healy, he had his head shoved so far up your ass
都可以从上面替你嚼食物了
he could chew your food for you.
所以我才不管是你还是别人干的呢
So frankly, I don't give a shit whether it was you or somebody else.
你把毒品放了进来
You let drugs in here.
一个女孩因你而死
A girl died because of you.
千里之堤毁于蚁穴
"A small leak can sink a great ship."
-知道这话谁说的吗  -不知道
- You know who said that? - No.
我也不知道  但我不允许我这儿有蚁穴
Neither do I. But I can't have leaky holes in my prison.
什么东西都别想进来  什么都别想出去
Nothing coming in, nothing going out.
接受退休吧  红妈
Welcome to retirement, Red.
找个爱好
Get a hobby,
给自己钩编个吊床吧  我才不管呢
crochet yourself a fucking hammock for all I give a shit.
混合大蒜  醋和辣椒酱
Use a mixture of garlic, vinegar and hot pepper sauce.
是天然杀虫剂
It's a natural insecticide.
停在停车场里  三小时后见
Park in the garage and I'll see you in three hours.
我知道的
I know the drill.
我最讨厌这部分了
I hate this part.
你真可怜
Poor you.
*几乎像是天堂*
*Almost paradise*
*我们已经敲响了天堂的大门*
*We're knockin' on heaven's door*
*几乎就是天堂*
*It's almost paradise*
*我们还有何求*
*How could we ask for more?*
天呐  真抱歉
Oh, my goodness, I am so sorry!
不  都怪我  真抱歉
No, that was me. Please, please.
不是的  是我太笨了
No! Oh, my God, I'm such a klutz.
没有的  不过你似乎需要多长几只手臂
Not at all. Just looks like you could use a couple more arms.
给你
Here you go.
我之前听说邮政业务要破产了呢
I heard the postal service was going bankrupt.
但你似乎要凭一己之力扭转局面呢
But it looks like you're personally gonna turn that around.
我尽力吧
Well... I do... I do what I can.
真是个爱国者啊
Yeah, a true patriot, huh?
是啊  我爱我的国家
Oh, yeah! I love my country.
要么你就是在搞邮政诈骗
Either that or you're running a mail scam.
是啊
Yes.
我来帮你吧
Here, let me help you with that.
谢谢你  你叫
Thank you. Thank you...
克里斯托弗
Uh, Christopher.
-克里斯托弗  -是啊
- Christopher. - Yeah.
抱歉  你长得有点像一个熟人
I'm sorry. You look like somebody.
我叫罗娜・莫里洛
I'm Lorna Morello.
长得漂亮又是意大利人  今天我好走运
Beautiful and Italian. Today must be my lucky day.
莫里洛小姐
Well, Miss Morello,
等你把这儿的邮票都用光了
after you're done cleaning this place out of postage,
或许我可以请你喝杯咖啡
maybe I could take you for a coffee?
好啊  克里斯托弗
I would love that, Christopher.
谢谢
Thank you.
这不是利奇菲尔德聪明的女发明家吗
Well, if it isn't the wily inventress of Litchfield
你就要挣大钱了
about to make a fortune for herself.
是啊
Ah, you know it.
但我想换个名字
Yo, but I'm thinking of changing the name.
你觉得"女士撒尿器"怎么样
What do you think about the "She-wee"?
我是指你另一个生意  做酒
No, I'm talking about your other little side business. Pruno.
我做的酒吗  那只是为了好玩  不要钱的
Oh, my hooch? That's just for fun. There's no charge.
女囚都会花钱买的
The girls would pay for it.
但不是为了钱啊
I mean, but that ain't the point.
我只是为自己和朋友做的
I make it for me and my friends.
但你在坐失良机
Yeah, but you're missing an opportunity.
而且  我有个超级棒的配方
Besides, I got me a killer recipe.
我们可以交换心得  弄个好酒出来
We could compare notes, tweak it a little bit.
按杯收钱
Charge by the cup.
按口收钱都行
Hell, we could charge by the sip.
不用了  我不想那么做  抱歉
Um, naw. That ain't my bag. Sorry.
你感觉怎么样了  气色好些了
How are you feeling? You look better.
不想让烧伤留疤吗
You want to keep a burn from scarring?
拿柠檬汁跟凡士林混合  每天涂抹
Mix some lemon juice with Vaseline, apply it every day.
你想怎么样
What do you want?
我想你别再生闷气了  我并没想害你受伤的
I want you to stop sulking. I never meant for you to get hurt.
我只是为了家族利益
I did it for the good of the family.
这还不够  红妈  不行
It's not good enough, Red. No.
好吧
Fine.
我能坐这儿吗
May I sit here?
当然  亲爱的
Of course, dear.
让桌子那头的那个男人别再冲我挤眉弄眼了
Tell that man at the end of the table to stop winking at me.
别看她吃东西  能把你逼疯
Don't watch her eat. It'll drive you insane.
她下周一才能把汤喝完
She'll finish that soup next Monday.
感觉不太对啊
This is not looking right.
因为你织得太紧了
Because you stitch too tight.
像我说的那样做个样本量具  数着针数
Make a gauge swatch like I told you and count your stitches,
这样就没问题了
you won't have that problem.
我们有个钩编会  想加入吗
We have a crochet circle if you'd like to join.
我不会钩编  不过听上去挺不错的
I don't crochet. But that sounds very nice.
无聊死了  但我们还能做什么呢
Oh, it's boring as hell. But what else have we got to do?
我的裤子呢
What happened to my pants?
你穿的那条吗
The ones you're wearing?
继续喝汤吧  吉米
You just work on that soup there, Jimmy.
这里就是一堆浆糊
Like a liquefied bowl of Jell-O.
我听得到  你个老婊子
I can hear you, you old cunt.
去你们这群贱人
Fuck these bitches.
别  我还没读完呢
No, I'm not done reading that!
书中人物都死了
Everybody dies.
-这是我的  -才不是呢
- This is mine. - No, it ain't.
那这背面为什么刻着我的囚犯编号
Then why does it have my inmate number carved in the back?
好吧  神探加吉特
Eh! Fine, Inspector Gadget.
加吉特根本不是个好侦探
Inspector Gadget was not a good detective.
他只是有很多工具
He just had a lot of stuff.
还有佩妮和智能脑帮他
Plus he had Penny and the Brain helping him.
你赶快给我滚吧
You best get the fuck out now.
难以置信  你也这样
This is unbelievable. You, too?
我们都以为你不会回来了
None of us thought you were coming back.
不是吧
Really?
不是为了看你  我喜欢沙滩
It ain't about you. I like the beach.
留着吧
Keep it.
那是我的毯子
That's my blanket.
不  这是克劳黛小姐的毯子
No, this is Miss Claudette's blanket.
是我的  我们都说过了  我要拿回来
It's mine. We've talked about this, and I'm taking it back.
是吗  你想怎么拿呢
Really? And how do you suppose you're going to do that?
我不想跟你打架
I don't wanna have to get physical with you.
得了
Oh, please!
我能像掰牙签一样掰断你的大腿  小瘦子
I could snap your femur like a toothpick, twiggy.
给我滚
Fuck off.
帕波  你在这儿啊
Piper! There you are. Hi.
听说今晚要看电影
Um, so, I heard tonight is movie night,
我还没有耳机  所以我去...
and I don't have headphones yet, so I went to...
你叫什么
What's your name?
总之  我没弄明白那个物资部的
Um, so, anyway, I guess I just don't understand
中国女人是什么意思
this Chinese lady at the commissary.
她是中国人吗
Is she Chinese?
我不想想当然  她可能是马来人呢
I don't wanna presume. She could be a Malay.
等会儿  布鲁克
Not now, Brook.
好吧  我们外面见吗
Okay, should I meet you out here?
我在忙呢  回你的铺位去  马上
I'm busy. Go back to your cube. Now.
好吧
Okay, yeah!
再见
Bye!
看来你给自己找了个宠物啊
Looks like you got yourself a pet kitten.
我真想把她装在一袋石头里
Oh, I just wanna put her in a bag of rocks
扔进湖底
and dump her at the bottom of the lake.
你真想要那条毯子吗
You really want that blanket?
或许我们可以做个交易
Maybe we could work out a trade?
这个尿道的事
All this pee hole business...
搞得我禁不住想我还有什么不知道的啊
Like, what the fuck else don't I know?
我活了这么久了
I been living all these years
从没看过我自己的阴道呢
and never even looked at my own damn vajayjay.
我的身体还会有什么让我意想不到的事啊
What other surprises my body gonna spring on me?
你看过你自己的脚吗
I mean, have you looked at these feet ever?
我不想吓着你
Like, I don't wanna scare you,
但我觉得这只可能不是脚趾头
but I'm not sure if this one right here's a toe.
-少来了  -小的这个看着不对劲啊
- Shut up. - Nah! The little one, it don't look right.
或许是铅笔橡皮擦  一块牛肉干
Could be a pencil eraser, old piece of jerky...
别拿我的脚寻开心
Oh, leave my feet alone!
反正我也弄完了
Yo, I'm done anyway.
看看我的杰作
Check out my masterpiece.
搞什么  真是乱死了
What? That's a hot-ass mess.
这叫抽象派
It's abstract, yo!
叫你涂指甲  不是皮肤  该死
You only supposed to paint the nail, not the skin! Fuck!
创新者的作品一开始总是受到批评
Look, all innovators have their work criticized at first.
你以后会喜欢的  我等着
Appreciation will come. I'll give you time.
我等过了
I already have time.
等来涂得稀巴烂的指甲
Time and a shit pedicure.
别闹了  你要弄花了
No! Stop! You're gonna mess it up!
-别闹了  -我块头比你大
- Stop! - I'm bigger than you, bitch!
我讨厌死挠痒痒了  上不来气啦
I hate tickling! No! No! Uncle! Uncle! I can't breathe!
抱歉  珀比
I'm sorry, P.
我们说过这事了
We've been through this.
我知道
I know.
-我不是  -我懂的
- I'm not... - I know.
或许我们可以抱一会儿
Maybe we could cuddle for a minute?
嗯
Yeah.
回去吧  你还可以回去
Go back. You can still go back.
看起来很有趣
That looks like fun.
你接受治疗多久了
So, how long you been in treatment?
我得在这儿坐两小时呢
Listen, I've gotta sit here for the next two hours,
我真不想跟一个秃头的老太太说话
and I don't really feel like talking to some old bald lady.
我们能装作我不在这儿吗
So can we just, like, pretend I'm not here?
我还打算给你讲笑话呢
I was gonna tell you a joke.
不用了  谢谢
I'm good, thanks.
电量低
护士  你们这里有iPhone的充电器吗
Yo, Nurse! Do you have an iPhone charger?
没有  抱歉
No, sorry.
天呐  这太扯了
Oh, my God! This is bullshit.
-你的笑话是什么  -太迟了
- What's your joke? - Too late.
随便你  肯定也不好笑
Whatever. I'm sure it's stupid.
医生对病人说
So, the doctor says to the patient,
"我有个坏消息  还有另一个坏的消息
"I got bad news and some more bad news.
坏消息是  你有癌症"
"The bad news is, you got cancer."
"那另一个更坏的消息呢"
"And the more bad news?"
"你还有老年痴呆症"
"You also got Alzheimer's disease."
病人想了一下  然后说
So, the patient thinks for a minute, and then she says,
"至少我没有癌症"
"Well, at least I don't have cancer!"
没听懂
I don't get it.
我不会解释的  自己想吧
I'm not gonna explain it to you. Figure it out.
我要去自动贩卖机那儿买饮料
I'm gonna grab a soda from the vending machine.
-要点什么吗  -百事吧
- Would you like anything? - I'd love a Pepsi.
别说出去哦
Don't tell anyone.
那是谁  你女儿吗
Who's that? Is she your daughter?
她是惩教官
She's a correctional officer.
-狱警吗  -没错
- Prison guard? - Exactly.
慢着  那么你是...
Wait. So you're not a...
是吗  真的吗
Are you? For serious?
我以为那只是老太太穿的化疗服呢
I thought those were just, like, comfy old lady chemo clothes.
你犯了什么事
What'd you do?
抢银行
Robbed a bank.
撒谎  不可能
You're lying. No way.
去谷歌啊
Google me.
好啊  说说吧
All right. Come on, tell me about it.
你想听第一次  还是最后一次
You want the first time or the last?
第一次是在1982年
The first time was in 1982...
管他呢
Fuck it.
舞池
库兹尼克夫妇诚邀您参加他们的女儿
安吉拉・库兹尼克和克里斯托弗・麦克拉伦的婚礼
2月14日周五  下午4点
睡前跟我吻别
爱住在这儿
垃圾  都是垃圾
Trash. Trash.
穿这件去参加《泽西海滩》节目太暴露了吗
This too much for the Jersey shore?
如果你是要去木板路上
Not if you're gonna walk the boardwalk
站街挣钱就不暴露
looking to make some extra cash.
这可是杜嘉班纳的衣服
Uh, it's Dolce & Gabbana, you nut.
你哪来的钱买这些东西的
How the heck are you paying for all this stuff?
我买的便宜  我会砍价
I get good deals. I'm a savvy shopper.
而且克里斯托弗喜欢我成熟的样子
And Christopher likes me to look sophisticated.
他说我像奥黛丽・赫本
He says I'm like Audrey Hepburn.
而且这是我们第一次一起去度周末
Besides, this is our first weekend away together.
-我们要住好酒店  -哪里
- And we're staying somewhere fancy. - Where?
不知道  他全都筹划好了
I don't know. He has the whole time planned.
他要带我去一艘帆船上
He is gonna take me on a sailboat,
日落的时候还要一起去坐怀尔伍德摩天轮
and then we're gonna ride the Wildwood Ferris Wheel at sunset.
真不敢相信我能遇见这么好的人  范妮
I can't believe I met a guy like this, Franny.
你该带他过来吃饭
You should bring him over for dinner.
见妈妈和其他人吗  你疯了吗
What, to meet Ma and everybody? Are you crazy?
我可不想他被吓跑  他是我的真命天子
I don't want him getting scared off, okay? He's the one.
如果没见过家人怎么知道他是真命天子
You don't know if he's the one until he's met the family.
这就像是测试
It's like a test.
他不需要什么测试  他是我的宿命
He don't need a test, okay? He's my destiny.
真的  就像是在电影里一样
And I'm telling you, it was like the movies.
就像在《诺丁山》里
Like, you know, in Notting Hill
休・格兰特和茱莉娅・罗伯茨撞在了一起
where Hugh Grant bumps into Julia Roberts
他把橙汁洒在了她身上
and he spills his orange juice on her?
我们就是这样
That's what happened to us.
我们撞上了彼此
We crashed into each other. Literally.
范妮  真的是天注定啊
I mean, Franny, it was meant to be.
你穿这裙子真好看
You look cute in that dress.
像《风月俏佳人》那样吗
Like Pretty Woman?
对  像《风月俏佳人》那样
Yeah, like Pretty Woman.
该死  长得像竹子一样快  简直是侵略
Bastards! They grow as fast as bamboo. It's an invasion.
我也会长这个
You know, I get them, too.
大部分时候是金色的  而且很软
Well, most of the time they're blonde, and they are soft,
但偶尔
but every once in a while,
也会长又黑又尖的
I do get one that is black and spiky,
如果不及时处理
and if you don't catch it in time,
它一下就能窜到两英尺
all of a sudden it's like two feet long
就从脸旁边戳出来
and it's growing right out of the side of your face,
像阴毛一样的胡子似的
like this giant, pubey, lady beard hair.
我这儿就有一根  莱瑞喊他"尖尖"
You know, I get one right here. Larry called him "Spike."
他怎么样了
How is he?
尖尖吗  刚起来  不过我能摸到了
Spike? Well, he's just starting up, but I can feel him.
我问你丈夫
The husband.
不知道  我们不说话  他也不写信
I don't know. We don't talk. No letters.
以前一周能收到两封
I used to get two a week.
这周我只收到奶奶寄来的一张卡片
In fact, this week, all I got was a card from my grandmother.
我的朋友最近也不怎么写东西了
My friends aren't feeling too prolific these days.
他肯定告诉他们我是个多可恶的出轨女
I'm sure he told them what a horrible, evil cheater I am.
我又没法为自己辩解
And it's not like I'm in any position to defend myself.
大家都不知道该跟我说什么
Nobody has any idea what to say to me.
人都这么操蛋
People are fickle fucks.
问题是  我不怪他们
You know, the thing is, I don't blame them.
我都不怪他  是我自私了
I don't even blame him, ultimately. I was selfish.
在这儿必须自私  这样才能生存
You have to be selfish in here. That's how you survive.
人的忠诚毫无意义
People's loyalty means nothing.
你对他们一失去用处  他们就会抛弃你
Because the second you're not useful to them, you're out.
你觉得你的姑娘们就是因为这个而跟你反目的吗
You think that's why your girls turned on you?
你听到的小道消息是这样的吗
Is that what you heard?
没有  只是我发现你最近总一个人
No. I've just noticed that you've been flying solo lately.
以前跟我做朋友有好处
My friendship used to come with perks.
现在我只是个凶巴巴的俄国老太太
Now I'm just an angry old Russian lady.
没了免费的长筒袜和眼线
Without the free stockings and eyeliner,
我不像过去那么吸引人了
I'm not quite the draw I used to be.
相信我  查普曼  丈夫没什么好的
And take it from me, Chapman, husbands are overrated.
像孩子一样没用  你算走运了
They're as useless as children. Count yourself lucky.
如果能长久  就不会出问题了
If it was meant to last, it would have.
拿去对付尖尖吧
Here. For Spike.
他一刻不停地哭  凌晨4点时
He cried nonstop. By 4:00 a.m.,
我都打算拿婴儿枕闷死他了
I was ready to smother him with a Boppy.
我知道这很阴暗
I know, that's really dark,
但7点新婴儿保姆来之前就只有我一个人
but I'm all alone until the new baby nurse comes at 7:00!
而且她3点就走  该死的
And then she leaves at 3:00! Fucking Pete.
如果我去阿拉斯加了怎么办
You know, what if I went off to Alaska?
不管他的  去乘皮船
Just, "Peace out! I'm off to kayak
装作自己是贝爷
and pretend I'm fucking Bear Grylls,
"我们搞出了一个童贞终结者
"'cause we spawned this symbolic end of childhood
现在我搞不定了  因为我就是长不大的彼得・潘"
and I can't handle it because I'm fucking Peter Pan."
我的心理治疗师是个白痴  歧视妇女的混蛋
My therapist is an idiot, misogynistic piece of shit.
你该去的  真的  去吧
You should go. Seriously, just go,
跟迷失男孩去划皮船
you know, kayak with the Lost Boys.
我留着这只小猴子
I'll keep this little monkey,
像养自己孩子一样  给他喂奶
breast-feed him, raise him as my own,
跟7点到3点服务的保姆一起照顾他
along with the baby nurse from 7:00 to 3:00.
她根本不性感  有点斜视  还有痤疮疤
She's not hot. She's got a wonky eye and bad acne scars.
而且都50多了
And she's in her 50s.
但她大蕉做得特别好
But she makes these amazing plantains
还给他唱吉米・克里夫的歌
and sings him Jimmy Cliff songs.
行啊
Sold.
只有你还跟我们一起出来
You're the only one who'll still hang out with us.
其他人都说还会过来看我们  但都不来了
Everyone swears they'll still come around, but they don't.
宝宝多大了
How old is the baby?
十周
Uh, ten weeks.
恭喜  你们这一家都真好看
Congratulations. Oh, you're such an attractive family.
谢谢  是啊
Thank you. Yeah, we...
虽然他有金发  但她说这绝对是我儿子
You know, despite the blond hair, she still swears he's mine.
他叫什么
What's his name?
汉普斯  汉普斯・兰斯勒  家族的名字
Hampus. Hampus Renselor. It's an old family name.
多美啊  小汉普
It's beautiful, isn't it? Little Hampy.
你们俩结婚多久了
How long have the two of you been married?
好久了  我们在地铁环线上结的婚
Long time. We got married on the Circle Line.
就在自由女神像前面
In front of the Statue of Liberty.
太美了  婚礼特别盛大
It was beautiful. Huge wedding.
-你们在城里相遇的吗  -嗯  是啊
- Did you meet in the city? - Oh, we... Yeah, we sure did.
在《星际迷航》的影迷会上
At a Star Trek convention.
我们都打扮成了克林贡人
Yeah, we were both dressed as Klingons.
这是我们的喜好
It's a passion of ours.
我立刻就知道她是真命天女
I knew right away she was the one.
祝你们开心  你们俩确实很般配
Well, enjoy. You're perfect together, it's very clear.
汉普斯  还不赖呢
Hampus. It's not half bad, actually.
或许还来得及改出生证明
There might still be time to change the birth certificate.
小汉普
"Little Hampy."
白人妞  拿盒子小心点
Blanca, careful with that box.
一共有多少
How many do we have in there?
请记录
Please let the record show
证人指认了被告
that the witness has indicated the defendant.
请继续  律师
Proceed, counselor.
请告诉庭上
Please tell the court
你是如何结识被告罗娜・莫里洛的
how you happen to know the defendant, Lorna Morello.
我们约会过一次
We went on one date.
我在邮局遇见了她  一起喝了杯咖啡
I met her at the post office and we had a coffee.
你们之间的关系就是如此吗
And that was the extent of your relationship?
我不想再进一步跟她发展了
I wasn't interested in pursuing things further.
我明确地告诉她了
I told her that. Very clearly.
那么莫里洛小姐
And did Miss Morello
在第一次约会之后还继续联系你了吗
continue to contact you after this initial date?
毫无休止  打电话  脸书留言
Relentlessly. Phone calls, Facebook messages,
发短信  邮件
texts, emails.
她跑去我家
She showed up at my house.
你是否明确向她表示你不喜欢她这些做法
Did you make it clear to her that these advances were unwanted?
是的  然后她开始威胁我
I did. And then I began receiving threats.
麦克拉伦先生
Now, Mr. MacLaren,
你是否采取措施制止她的行为了呢
did you take any action to prevent these advances?
我换了手机号  我的电邮账号  搬了两次家
I changed my phone number, my email account, and I moved twice.
每次都被她找到
Each time, she found me.
我开始约会我现在的女友安吉拉后
When I started dating my current girlfriend, Angela,
我们去亚特兰大度周末时她也跑了来
she showed up in Atlantic City, where we'd gone for the weekend.
她在我车上留字条  朝我草坪上扔垃圾
She left notes on my car, she threw trash on my lawn,
给我留语音信息
she left voicemails yelling about
说我都不帮忙养狗
how I wasn't helping enough with the dog.
我根本没有狗
I don't even have a dog.
然后她还威胁要掐死安吉拉
And then she threatened to strangle Angela.
这时候我就申请了禁止令
And that's when I got a restraining order.
她有企图伤害你吗
Did she ever make an attempt on your life?
是的  我们在安吉拉车下面找到了一个自制炸弹
Yes. We found a homemade explosive device under Angela's car.
他太夸张了  他们根本在扭曲事实
Oh, he's being so dramatic. They're twisting this whole story.
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
安吉拉  安吉拉  亲爱的
Hey, Angela. Angela? Babe?
看看啊  地上一堆碎玻璃
Look at this. There's glass all over the floor.
喂
Hello?
有人吗
Is anyone in here?
你说得对  卡普托
You were right, Caputo.
-什么对  -我累了
- About? - I'm tired.
我老了  这是人生的新阶段  该消停了
I'm getting old. It's a new phase of life. Time to pack it in.
很高兴听你这么说
I'm glad to hear it.
我现在正式是老年金花团之一了
I'm officially one of the Golden Girls, hmm?
午餐时跟她们坐在一起
I sit with them at lunch.
她们甚至邀我加入她们的手工会
They've even asked me to join their craft circle.
你来我办公室干什么
What are you doing in my office?
你让我找个爱好  我们的确就需要个爱好
You told me to find a hobby, and that's exactly what we need.
尤其是对于那些年纪大的  其他女人都有活儿干
Especially the old ladies. The rest of the women here have work.
而这些年纪大的根本没有自己的活动
There's no programs for those who've been put out to pasture.
你想让她们做什么  水中健身舞吗
What do you suggest? Aquarobics?
-听说园艺很能修养身心  -没错
- I hear gardening is very therapeutic. - It is.
减轻压力  有助改善抑郁
It lowers stress, helps with depression.
把手插进泥土里  料理一个活物
There's something about actually putting your fingers in the dirt,
对人很有帮助
nurturing something to life.
我从书中看到说  这能修身养性
I've read it can be very healing.
每周做三小时园艺的人
People who do three hours of gardening a week
能活得更长  这可是真的
actually live longer. It's a fact.
地勤用的那个老棚屋
That old shed we use on grounds crew,
以前是个温室  对吧
it used to be a greenhouse, no?
把那里打扫出来  让它重换生机  不会太难
Wouldn't be so hard to clean it out, bring it to life.
让那些老家伙们去鼓捣鼓捣
Let the old codgers tinker around.
还可以把你的小植物放那儿呢
There's even a place to put your little plants,
别总放在办公室窗边
besides your office window.
一看就是没晒够太阳
From the look of them, they're not getting the sun they need.
对你有什么好处
What do you get out of it?
可以再次使唤人
I get to boss people around again.
哪怕是一群老化石
Even if it is a bunch of fossils.
菲格不会同意启动新项目的
Fig would never go for a new program.
花不了多少钱
It wouldn't cost much.
拿出预算来  种子  土  都写在纸上
Bring me a budget. Seeds, soil, everything spelled out on paper.
我想想办法
I'll see what I can do.
-真抱歉  -怎么了
- I'm so sorry! - For what?
我刚刚睡着了  忘了时间
I just... I fell asleep. I don't know what time it is.
没事  我们刚完事  你来得正好
No worries. We just finished. You're right on time.
你没事吧  莫里洛
You okay, Morello?
挺好的  进行的怎么样  罗莎
Oh, yeah, yeah, I'm fine, fine. How did it go, Rosa?
你还是开车吧
Maybe you should just drive.
我一直以为是便便的洞
I always thought it was one pooter hole
旁边还有几个洞洞
and a couple of different holes off of it,
像是一堆岩洞
like a cave system or something.
有时候  我尿尿像洒水车那样
Now, see, sometimes my pee comes out like a sprinkler.
都不是一股的  更像是
Like, it's not a steady stream. It's more like...
小淋浴头
like a mini shower head.
你听到了吗
Are you listening to this?
现在的热门话题呢  神奇的女性解剖学
It's the talk of the town. The wonders of the female anatomy.
真得有人给这些女人找本医学书来
You know, someone needs to get these women a medical book.
简直太可笑了
This is ridiculous.
你知道吗
Do you know?
大体上是知道的
I mean... generally.
记得你当年也是那样吗  查普曼
Remember when that was you, Chapman?
茫然不知所措  想找个地方坐下
A lost little kumquat looking for a place to sit.
她为什么进来的
What's she in for?
政治抗议
Some kind of political protest.
你们俩或许有很多共同语言呢
You know, the two of you might have a lot to talk about.
我看不会
I doubt that.
这些假波西米亚小孩儿
These bogus bohemian babies
根本不知道什么叫非武力直接行动
have no idea what a non-violent direct action is.
一群假嬉皮士
Dirty, fake hippies.
某人火气不小啊
Someone's got some issues.
布鲁克  过来坐
Brook! Right here!
别这样  她是个话唠
Please don't do that. She's a gabber.
我们走吧
Shall we adjourn?
明智
I think that's wise.
天呐  真是松了口气  我以为你生我气了呢
Oh, my God, I am so relieved. I thought you were mad at me.
你没生我气吧
You're totally not mad at me, right?
当然没了
No, of course I'm not mad at you.
谢天谢地  这里每个人都一直气冲冲的
Thank God. Everyone in here is in such a bad mood all the time.
我一直以为女子监狱
I mean, like, I always thought women's prison would be
是团结一心  女性力量什么的
more about community and girl power and stuff.
但这里有些女人真是疯了
But some of these women just seem crazy.
情况还能更糟的  布鲁克
It can be a lot worse than that, Brook.
这里有时候会很危险
It can be seriously dangerous in here.
别犯傻了
Don't kid yourself.
什么意思
What do you mean?
你长得不错  你会被人盯上的
You're a pretty girl. And you're gonna be a target.
我当初就是
I know that I was.
你是说被强奸吗
You mean like rape?
强奸  袭击  暴打
Ooh, rape, assault, battery.
你得给自己找个狱中妻
You need to find yourself a prison wife.
很彪悍  没人敢惹的那种
Somebody really tough. Somebody nobody's gonna fuck with.
你也是这样吗
Did you do that?
我只是说  找对了保护者  跟她睡一晚
All I'm saying is that one night with the right protector
整个服刑期间你都不用担心了
can keep you safe for the rest of your sentence.
你是指你吗
You mean you.
不  我不够彪悍
No. See, I'm not tough.
你需要一个能让人害怕的人
What you need is somebody who inspires real fear.
比较男性化  大块头的那种
You know, somebody who's kind of man-ish and kind of bulky,
但心地温柔
but tender at heart.
而且好选择不多  大部分都有主了
And there's not a lot of good ones. Most of them are taken.
二位说什么呢
Hey, you two. What are we talking about here?
我今天觉得好孤单啊
Well, you know, I am feeling so single today.
怎么回事
What's going on?
没什么  大嘣  这是布鲁克
Nothing. Big Boo, this is Brook.
布鲁克  这是大嘣
And, Brook, this is Big Boo.
这是什么游戏吗  我不懂
Is this some kind of game? I don't get it.
怎么回事啊
What is going on?
你干这个真是烂到家了
Could you suck any more at this?
我烂  看看你的时机多差劲啊
I suck at this? I mean, look at your ridiculous timing.
显然这样不行  能把毯子还我吗
Clearly this is not working, so can I just have my blanket back?
不行  你没给我我要的
No! You didn't deliver.
给她什么  我吗
Deliver what? Me?
我该做的都做了
I did my part.
你是要把我卖了吗
Were you trying to pimp me out?
她拿了我的毯子
She took my blanket.
那本来是我室友的  对我意义重大
It belonged to my roommate, it meant a lot to me.
而且  宿舍里太他妈冷了
Plus, it is very fucking cold in the dormitories.
你要为了一条毯子卖了我
You tried to sell me for a blanket?
你要这么说的话
Well, when you put it that way...
你真有病  你知道吗
You are sick, you know that?
你真的很有病
You are seriously fucked up.
她说得对  查普曼  你真是个坏人
You know, she's right, Chapman. You're a horrible person.
你怎么了
Hey, hey, what's the matter?
想谈谈吗
You wanna talk about it?
天呐
Oh, my God!
我以前只跟一个女孩这么做过
You know, I've only ever done this with one other girl before.
好像是在波纳罗
I think it was at Bonnaroo,
我跟一个画我胸部的女人接吻
and I made out with the chick who painted my breasts.
我们都戴着很大的头巾
We were both wearing these, like, big headdresses
而且放着SCI的歌
and, like, The String Cheese Incident was playing,
我们上了舞台开始跳舞
and we got up on stage and we just started dancing.
其实想起来
You know, when I think back on it,
我后来好像中暑了
I think I probably ended up getting heat stroke
因为帐篷里简直热极了
'cause the tent was like 1,000 degrees.
感觉好棒
That feels good.
你有没有过这感觉  你在自己身体里
Do you ever feel like you're in your body,
但又能感觉到周围的空间
but you can really feel, like, the space around you, like,
就好像周围的空气突然变得很沉重
air suddenly becomes, like, really heavy,
你能感受到整个大气
and you can feel, like, the atmosphere,
和分子都萦绕在你周围
and the molecules, just hanging around your head.
然后感到一种刺痛
And then, you feel this tingling...
来吧
There we go.
SC什么I啊
Fucking String Cheese.
你的抱抱兔呢
Where's your little cuddle bunny?
什么
What?
我看见那天的事了
I saw what went down in here.
你跟你女朋友温存来着
You all cozied up with your little girlfriend.
我不是同性恋
I ain't gay.
我看着挺像的
Looked pretty gay to me.
我们只是朋友
We just friends.
是吗  只是朋友
Yeah? Just friends?
你很寂寞  想要有人抚摸  抱抱
And you're lonely. You wanna be touched. Need a hug.
或许不止是拥抱
Maybe even more than a hug.
想要个属于自己的人
Need all that drama of someone to call your own.
我告诉你吧
Let me tell you something.
境遇性同性恋都是那些
Gay-for-the-stay is for punk ass bitches
不够坚强  不能维持真我的贱人
who aren't strong enough to be true to themselves.
我说了  我不是那样的
I told you, I ain't like that.
我知道  我也知道等你出去
I know that. And I also know that when you get out of here,
你不希望你的邻居
you don't want people on the block
说你干过那种事
talking about how you went that way.
所以告诉你
That's why I'm telling you,
别被她拉进那种破事里
do not let her drag you into that shit.
她不是你真正的朋友  只是号子里的朋友
She is not your real friend. She is only your friend in here.
她不像我那么了解你
She doesn't know you like I do.
我看不出来他到底是不是在呼吸
I can't really tell if he's breathing on here.
你觉得他像死了吗
Does he look dead to you?
是啊  不像啦
Yes. No.
不  他就是睡着了  谢天谢地
No, he's asleep. He is blissfully asleep.
他真可爱  是吧
He's so cute, right?
他睡着的时候真完美
When he's sleeping, he's perfect.
我很喜欢今天跟你玩过家家
I loved playing house with you today.
不知道我以后还能不能有这种生活了
I don't know if I'm ever gonna have that.
能的  少来了你
Yeah, you will. Shut the fuck up.
我不想回家
I don't want to go home.
很好  我也不想你回家
Good. I don't want you to.
你拯救了我的人生  让我不至于疯掉
You're saving my life and my sanity.
而且你还会换尿布
Plus, you change diapers.
而且我用剩的牙买加菜就能打发你
And I can pay you with leftover Jamaican food.
说真的  莱瑞
Honestly, Larry,
这周要是没有你我真熬不过去了
I really wouldn't have made it through this week without you.
谢谢
Thank you.
别幼稚了  听好了  好好学
Now, don't be so juvenile, ladies. Listen up and learn, okay?
这是你们的阴道  这里是小阴唇
Now, this is your vagina. This is your labia minora,
这里是阴蒂  这里是尿道
this, this is your clitoris, and this is your urethra.
你们就从这儿尿尿
This is where you pee from.
姑娘们  今晚  你们每个人
Now, ladies, I want each and every one of you
回到自己的铺位上
to go back to your bunks tonight
熟悉一下自己的洞洞
and get to know your own chachas, okay?
不是吧  我还有个阴阜
No fucking way. I got a mons pubis.
没错  你还有大阴唇  和阴蒂包皮
Yes, you do. And you also have a labia majora and a clitoral hood.
那些找不到自己阴蒂
Now for those of you who are having trouble finding your clitoris,
或是你们的伴侣找不到你们的阴蒂的人
or your partner is having trouble finding your clitoris,
你可能要掀开阴蒂包皮  才能看得到
you might have to pull back the clitoral hood to expose it.
这很少有人知道
Little known fact.
我用这张票  就算是被纽约打败了
The day I use this ticket is the day New York has beaten me.
我刚刚注意到一点  你过得不太好呢
You know, I just noticed something. You're kind of a mess.
多谢了
Thank you.
不  我是说  没人跟你说过吗
Nah, I mean, did anybody ever tell you that?
你是第一个
You're the first.
她们凭什么能坐好座位了
Since when do they get all the best seats?
白人的统治结束了
The reign of whitey is over.
这部电影我还没看过呢
I've never seen this movie before,
但这里面满是资本主义的宣传
but this is some serious capitalist propaganda.
为什么这就叫成功了
I mean, why is that success?
我们就非要在角落办公室里工作
Are we all supposed to wanna work in a corner office
挣一堆钱吗
and make butt-loads of money?
完全是企业的宣传
It's a total corporate agenda.
混蛋
Asshole.
想要吗
You want it?
天呐  你真是...
Oh, my... You know...
西班牙婊子坐的垫子太高了
Yo, the Spanish bitches are sitting on too many freakin' pillows,
我们都看不见东西了
making it hard to see and shit.
你喊我什么
What'd you call me?
想当年  黑人女人能...
Shit. In my day, the black women would have done...
是啊  我们知道  这里是你们的
Yeah, yeah, we know. Y'all ran this place.
该死  我都错过半场电影了
Shit, I missed, like, half the movie.
我的座位在哪
Where my seat at?
抱歉
Sorry.
你没给我留座吗  你总给我留座的啊
You didn't save me a seat? You always save me a seat.
你知道她们都什么样
You know how people are.
怎么了
What?
或许你该早点来
Maybe you should get here on time.
我做过很多蠢事
I've done a lot of stupid things.
我猜也是
I bet you have.
但我从没跟有妇之夫有过纠葛
But I have never, ever been involved with a married man.
我们开始的时候他们已经分居了
Well, he was sort of separated when we started.
但其实不是那么回事
Yeah, well, it turned out to be a lie.
真是个天大的错误
The whole thing was a mistake.
但我们吸取教训  继续生活
But we live and we learn and we move on...
你还好吗
Are you okay?
没事  我就是...
I'm fine. I'm just...
想我未婚夫克里斯托弗了
I'm missing my fiance, Christopher, is all.
亲爱的  深呼吸
Oh, honey. Deep breaths.
时间过得很快的  你们不久就又能在一起了
Time is all relative. You'll be together before you know it.
而且会结婚  我们会结婚的
And married. We'll be married.
当然了
Of course you will.
我决定不戴面纱了  太老套了
I've decided not to wear a veil. It's too traditional.
我要他看着我的脸
And I want him to see my face.
何必遮起来呢  你美极了
Why hide it? It's gorgeous.